import "Catalog/catalog.css";


// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],

}



export var cards = {
  
  //#region Table de 16
  "0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "22"
  },
  "3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "33"
  },
  "4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "44"
  },
  "5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "55"
  },
  "6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "66"
  },
  "7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "77"
  },
  "8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "88"
  },
  "9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "99"
  },
  "10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "110"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 16
 
  //#region Table de 17
  "17x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "17x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "17"
  },
  "17x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "34"
  },
  "17x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "51"
  },
  "17x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "68"
  },
  "17x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "85"
  },
  "17x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "102"
  },
  "17x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "119"
  },
  "17x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "136"
  },
  "17x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "153"
  },
  "17x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '17 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "170"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 17

  //#region Table de 18
  "18x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "18x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "18x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "36"
  },
  "18x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "54"
  },
  "18x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "72"
  },
  "18x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "90"
  },
  "18x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "108"
  },
  "18x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "126"
  },
  "18x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "144"
  },
  "18x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "162"
  },
  "18x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "180"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 18

  //#region Table de 19
  "19x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "19x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "19"
  },
  "19x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "38"
  },
  "19x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "57"
  },
  "19x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "76"
  },
  "19x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "95"
  },
  "19x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "114"
  },
  "19x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "133"
  },
  "19x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "152"
  },
  "19x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "171"
  },
  "19x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '19 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "190"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 19

  //#region Table de 20
  "20x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "20x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "20"
  },
  "20x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "40"
  },
  "20x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "60"
  },
  "20x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "80"
  },
  "20x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "100"
  },
  "20x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "120"
  },
  "20x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "140"
  },
  "20x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "160"
  },
  "20x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "180"
  },
  "20x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '20 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "200"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 20
};